cosmeticdentistryguide.co.uk 2018-05-13

# Privacy Policy | Cosmetic dentistry guide

Cosmeticdentistryguide.co.uk is firmly committed to the privacy of information provided by visitors to our websites. We actively comply with the UK Data Protection Act 1998.  

**The information we collect**

We only collect identifiable information that is specifically and voluntarily provided by a visitor to our sites. Generally this includes name, email address, cosmetic procedure of interest, and other similar contact information. Any personal data supplied to cosmeticdentistryguide.co.uk will be used solely for the purpose indicated on the web page requesting the information to enable us to better understand the visitors requirements.  
To alter or remove your details

We would ask that you keep us informed via our contact form of any changes in your personal data or if you wish to have your details removed so that we may keep our records up to date at all times.  
Disclosure of personal information

cosmeticdentistryguide.co.uk will not sell, rent, trade or otherwise supply to third parties any personal information obtained from visitors unless required to do so in the process of helping the visitor find the required treatment at the required venue. We will not disclose any personal information provided unless you have authorised us to so do, or if we are required to do so by law.  

**Cookies**

The advertisements served on this site by 3rd parties may use "cookies". A "cookie" is a small file that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. Should you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognise your browser. This system is used by many websites and is common place on the internet. Cookies may store user preferences and other simple information, however, it will not identify you personally. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly with cookies disbaled.  

**Visitor Statistics**

We do collect data from visitors browsers using a third party analytics service to enable us to know general details of where they came from, what region of the world and what pages they visited. This in itself is not individually identifying data except for the IP address. This type of data collection for website visitor statistics is common to most websites.  
Access to data

You have the right to be told what personal information we hold about you on our databases. Should you require this you should fill out a query via the contact form on our website.
